YUSUF CEYLAN

STUDENT 3D AND VFX ARTIST

CONTACT

+447585344987

josefceylan@gmail.com

yusuftceylan.github.io

http://www.linkedin.com/in/yusuft ceylan/

SKILLS

3d, 2D Design

3d, 2D Animation

VFX

Shaders and Texturing

Blender, Maya

FL Studio, Bandlab

Unity, Unreal Engine

Html, Css, JavaScript

C#, C++

September 2021 - present UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH

BSc Games Design and Development

LANGUAGES

English

Turkish



PROFILE

I am currently a Games development student at the University of Greenwich,

specializing in VFX, 3D-2D modeling, and animation. I am passionate about

developing video games, specifically when it comes to making artwork in

games. I have experienced challenges that come with a team and developed myself

by attending group projects and game jams at the university. However, I have specifically

experienced teamwork under stress with limited time in the places I have worked.

I am currently working as a part-time worker.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chef

Zuzu Bistron Bar

2023-Present

- work in a restaurant team as a chef that changes frequently
- put the same amount of effort for every single food I need to prepare for long hours
- know how to communicate with my team
- We are regularly forced to solve problems in a spesific period of time and find different solutions.

YUSUF CEYLAN

STUDENT 3D AND VFX ARTIST

Chef, Manager

Dads Bao & Burger

2021-2023

- I worked in a small kitchen wher I learned new skills at the first and started managing it after a while.
- Worked under pressure with limited time
- One of my jobs was to teach the new employers how everything worked and help them gain the skills required to work efficiently
- Since it was a small place, I learned how to get a work done by myself and solve problems without having anyone to get help from.

3D Designer

Hype 2024-2024

- I made models and animations for a small amount of people in a team called hype
- It was more of a small project than a job to me since I only worked with them for a month.
- My duty was to model animate some small scenes for their advertisements.
- The scenes were use on their social media accounts

HOBBIES

- Playing games
- Producing sounds and musics for games
- Producing music for cinematics
- Reading book
- Training
- Watching videos about science
- Drawing





